Oh,here's little Ben falling asleep.
哦,小本本困了
A little bit later. Is he gonna sleep?
等一下,他就要睡著了
Is he gonna sleep? Is he gonna?
他要睡了嗎?要睡了嗎?
Yep,out like a light!
是的,就是這個了!
This sure trumps the "Has he pooped?" series.
這一定是強普的「他筋疲力竭了?」系列
Ross,we love him,okay?
羅斯,我們愛他,ok?
But right now he's just a little fat guy.
但是現在他只是一個裸體的胖小伙
How excited can we get?
我們實在是太興奮了?
-What you got? -400 pictures of Ben on a rug.
-你拿的什麼? -本墊子下的400張照片
-Oh,my God! -Let me see!
-哦,天哪! -讓我看看!
The One Where Rachel Finds Out
六人行 第1季 第24集 瑞秋恍然大悟
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Here's little Ben nodding off.
小本本睡著了
Look at Aunt Monica's little boy!
看摩妮卡姑姑的小男孩
-Look,he's got Ross haircut. -Let me see.
-瞧,他有羅斯的髮型. -我看看
Oh,God! Is he just the sweetest thing?
天啊,真可愛
You must just wanna kiss him all over.
你一定想吻遍他
That would be nice.
那感覺一定很好
-Pardon? -Nothing.
-什麼? -沒事
Just a little extra air in my mouth.
只是嘴裡有多餘的空氣
Chan,can you help me out? I'll pay you back.
錢德,願意幫我嗎?我保證一定會還的
Right. Including the waffles last week,you now owe me...
好,包括上星期的威化餅,你現在欠我
... 1 7 jillion dollars.
17大洋
-Really,I'll pay you back this time. -Where's this money coming from?
-真的,這一次我真的會還 -錢將從哪兒來?
I'm helping out at the NYU Med School with research.
我正幫紐約大學醫學院做一些研究
What kind of research?
什麼研究?
Just,you know,science.
只不過,你知道的,科學研究
Science.
科學?
Yeah,I think I've heard of that.
我想我聽說過
It's a fertility study.
生殖研究
Joey,please tell me you're only donating your time.
喬伊,請告訴我你只貢獻時間
Actually,a little more than that.
事實上,比這稍微多一點點
Thank you,God. This will bring us so much joy.
謝謝,上帝.這會給我們帶來更多笑料
Come on,it's not that big a deal.
拜託,這沒什麼了不起的
I just go down there every other day...
我只是兩天去一趟
...and make my contribution to the project.
對此計劃貢獻己力
But at the end of two weeks, I get $700!
但兩周後我就有七百元
You're gonna be making money hand over fist.
你將「靠手」賺錢
That's funny. Very funny.
這太有趣了,非常有趣
This is great. I actually know somebody who loves what they do.
太好了,我真的知道有人非常喜歡他們做的
But what do you do to unwind after a tough day at work?
但是一天的辛苦工作後,你怎麼放鬆自己呢?
Okay,we got the coleslaw and buns.
我們有酸捲心菜絲,小麵包
The ground-up flesh of formerly cute cows and turkeys.
還有絞牛肉及火雞肉
I just love barbecuing with you.
我喜歡和你一起出去烤肉
Men are here!
男人回來了
We make fire.
我們生火
Cook meat.
煮肉
Put out fire by peeing, no get invited back.
然後撒尿熄火,從此成為拒絕往來戶
Cute.
真逗
-Melanie called. She'll be late. -Okay.
-瑪蓮妮來電說她會遲到. -好
How are things going? Is she becoming your "special someone"?
你們倆進展得如何?她會成為你的女友?
I don't know. She's pretty great.
我不知道,她很好
What does she think of your little science project?
是嗎?她對你的研究計劃有何感想?
You think I'd tell a girl I like that I'm also seeing a cup?
你認為我會告訴她,我也和「杯子」約會?
Man's got a point.
男人是有重點的
The tough thing is, she really wants to have sex.
麻煩的是她想和我做愛
Crazy bitch.
這娘兒們瘋了
I got a week left to go. According to the rules...
此計劃我只剩一星期,根據規定
... I can't conduct personal experiments,if you know what I mean.
如果我想拿到錢,我就不能做「個人」實驗 如果你們懂我意思的話
Joey,we always know what you mean.
喬伊,我們永遠都瞭解你
How long did you think this barbecue would last?
你以為烤肉會維持多久?
-I'm going to China. -Jeez,you say one thing,and....
-我要去中國了 -你說一件事…
-China? -For the museum. Someone found a bone.
-你要去中國? -對,為博物館出差,有人找到骨頭
They don't want us to have it.
我們要骨頭,但他們不想給我們骨頭
I'm going to try to persuade them. It's a whole big bone thing.
因此派我去說服他們給我們骨頭,都是骨頭的事
Anyway,I'll be gone for a week.
總之,我要去一個星期
If you want to reach me,you can't. So here's my itinerary.
你們將連絡不到我,這是我的行程表
-Here's a picture of me. -Oh,let me see.
-這是我的照片. -讓我看
Could you show it to Ben every now and then so he doesn't forget me?
能偶爾拿照片到卡蘿家去給本看? 這樣他就不會忘記我了
"Hi,Ben. I'm your father."
本,我是你爸爸
"I am The Head!"
我是頭
This barbecue's gonna be very fun.
這回烤肉一定很好玩
I wanted to wish Rachel a happy birthday before I left.
瑞秋在嗎?我想在我離開前祝她生日快樂
-She's out having drinks with Carl. -Hey,who's Carl?
-她和卡爾在外面喝酒 -卡爾是誰?
That guy she met at the coffeehouse.
她在咖啡屋認識的那個
-There's this guy she met at -The coffeehouse? Right.
-她在咖啡屋認識的那個? -咖啡屋?是的
So you do know who he is.
這麼說你知道他是誰
I'll go say goodbye to the guys.
我去跟他們道別
Hey,you know what? Tell them that bone story.
告訴他們骨頭的事吧
-I have to go to China. -The country?
-我得到中國(瓷器)一趟 -國家?
No,this big pile of dishes in my mom's breakfront.
不,我媽家中的一大堆盤子
Do you know who Carl is?
你知道卡爾是誰嗎?
Let's see. Alvin,Simon,Theodore.... No.
我想看看,艾文,賽門,希爾朵…不認識
Rachel's having drinks with him tonight.
瑞秋今晚和他在一起喝酒
How can she,when she's never shown interest in you?
不,她還沒對你有任何表示前,怎能這樣做?
-Forget about her. -He's right.
-忘了她吧 -他說得對
Please move on. Go to China. Eat Chinese food.
去吧,到中國,吃中國菜
Of course,there they just call it "food."
當然,他們在那兒只稱為菜
Yeah,I guess. I don't know.
是嗎?大概吧,我也不知道
All right,just give her this for me,okay?
幫我把這個交給她
We're looking out for you. We want you to be happy.
兄弟,我們只是為你著想,我們要你快樂
I may only have a couple beers in me,but I love you.
或許我喝了兩瓶,但我愛你
I'm still on my first.
我只喝了一瓶
I just think you're nice.
我覺得你人真好
That's when we started this fruit basket business.
總之,我和朋友開始水果籃事業後
We call ourselves "The Three Basketeers."
我們就自稱為「三籃人」
Like "The Three Musketeers," only with fruit.
就像「三個火槍手」,只不過是用蔬菜啊
-How do you want your burgers? -Presents first!
-誰想吃漢堡? -不,禮物先
We're doing presents first.
禮物先,待會兒再吃
Hey,hold on there,tiger. How are you holding up?
等等,猛男.進展得如何?
Well,not so good. She thinks tonight we're gonna...
不太順利,她想在今晚
...complete the transaction, if you know what And you do.
就敲定這筆交易,如果你…你懂
Have you ever thought about being there for her?
曾想過要為她著想?
What do you mean?
什麼意思?
You know,just be there for her.
你知道的,只為她著想
Not following you.
不懂
Think about it.
考慮一下
Okay. I'm guessing this is from....
我猜這是…
-Thank you,Melanie. -This one right here is from me.
-謝謝,瑪蓮妮. -這是我送你的
Okay. It's light. It rattles.
好輕,還有聲音
It's...
這是…
...Travel Scrabble!
…是旅遊拼字
Thank you.
謝謝
This one's from Joey.
這是喬伊送的
It feels like a book,I think it's a book. And it's a book!
感覺像是一本書,我猜是一本書,就是一本書啊!
It's Dr. Seuss!
是「蘇博士」
That book got me through some tough times.
那本書讓我度過許多難關
There's a little child inside this man.
這男人裡面有個小孩
The doctors say if they remove it, he'll die.
醫生說把他移走他就會死
-Who's this from? -From Ross.
-這是誰送的? -羅斯送的
Oh,my God! He remembered!
天啊,他記得
-Remembered what? -lt was months ago.
-記得什麼? -幾個月前
We walked by this antique store. I saw this pin.
我們經過一家古董店.我看見這個胸針時
I told him it was like one my grandma had when I was little.
我告訴他我小時候我祖母也有一個
I can't believe he remembered!
沒想到他還記得
Well,sure,but can you play it on a plane?
但你能在飛機上玩嗎?
It's so pretty! This must've cost him a fortune.
-好漂亮 -一定花了他不少錢
I can't believe it.
沒想到他會這麼做
Remember when he fell in love with Carol...
記得大學時代他和卡蘿相戀時
...and bought her that expensive crystal duck?
他送她一隻貴死人的水晶鴨?
What did you just say?
你剛說什麼?
Crystal duck.
水晶鴨
No,no,no. The "love" part?
不,相戀那一部份
-Oh,my God! -Oh,no,no,no.
-天啊! -糟了,糟了
That's good. Just keep rubbing your head. That'll turn back time.
很好,繼續撓你的頭,時間會倒流的
This is unbelievable. I mean,this is unbelievable!
太不可思議了,真是太不可思議了
I know. This is really,really huge.
我知道,這真是太大了
No,it's not. It's small. It's tiny. It's petite. It's wee.
不,它又小又細又霉
I don't think any of our lives will ever be the same ever again.
我認為我們的生活將產生變化
Is there a mute button on this woman?
這女人身上有消音裝置嗎?
I think this is so great. I mean,you and Ross!
我認為這樣很好啊,你和羅斯
-Did you have any idea? -No,none!
-你有感覺嗎? -沒有
My first night in the city, he mentioned asking me out...
我來到紐約的第一夜,他曾提過要約我出去
... but nothing ever happened.
但他後來再沒提過邀我出去
What else did he say? Does he wanna go out?
他還說些什麼?,他想約我出去?
Given that he's in love with you...
如果他愛你愛得無法自拔
... he wouldn't mind getting a cup of coffee.
他大概想和你喝杯咖啡什麼的
Ross? All this time? I've gotta talk to him.
羅斯?這些日子以來?我得找他談談
-He's in China! -The country.
-可他現在中國! -那個國家
Is his flight gone?
她的飛機起飛了嗎?
Yes! He's watching a woman do this:
是的!他正在看一個女人做這個:
He's gone!
他走了!
His flight doesn't leave for 45 minutes.
他的飛機再過45分鐘才會起飛
-What about time difference? -From here to the airport?
-時差呢? -從這兒到機場?
-You'll never make it! -I've gotta try.
-你趕不上的! -我得試試
What'll you say to him?
瑞秋,你要對他說什麼?
-I don't know. -Then you shouldn't go.
-我也不知道 -那麼或許你不該去
Right. If you're gonna break his heart,that can wait.
沒錯,因為你是去傷他的心,不妨再等等
But if it's good,tell him now.
對,但如果是好消息,你得立刻去
-Maybe I'll know when I see him. -All right,does this help?
-或許見到面時我就知道 -這個有幫助嗎?
No. Look,all I know is,I cannot wait a week. This is just too big.
沒有,我只知道我等不了一星期, 這件事太嚴重了
I've just gotta talk to him. Okay,I'll see you later.
我得和他談談,再見了
Rachel,I love you! Deal with me first!
瑞秋,我愛你.先跟我把事情解決
All right.
好吧
-Ross! Excuse me,pardon me. -Your boarding pass?
-羅斯,抱歉 -請出示登機證
I need to talk to my friend.
我沒有,我只是想找我朋友
Sorry,you're not allowed here without a pass.
抱歉,除非有登機證,否則不能進人
He's right there, in the blue jacket! Can l?
他就在那兒,穿藍色夾克
I'm sorry. Federal regulations!
對不起,不行,聯邦法規
Then could you please just give him a message for me?
好吧,能請你傳話給他?
-This is very important. -All right. What's the message?
-這件事非常重要 -好吧,請說
I don't know.
我也不知道
Excuse me,sir! Excuse me,sir? I have a message for you.
抱歉,先生!有人叫我傳話給你
Rachel loved the present. She'll see you when you get back.
是瑞秋!她說她喜歡你送的禮物 你回來後她想見你
What?
什麼?
Toby,I don't know what she's talking about.
桃伊,拜託,我不懂她在說什麼
There's no Rachel. Don't give me that deep freeze.
我不認識瑞秋,別給我臉色看
Oh,Joey,Joey,Joey!
哦,喬伊,喬伊,喬伊!
I think I blacked out there for a minute.
我想我爽昏了啊
It was nothing.
這不算什麼
Well,now we gotta find something fun for you.
現在讓我來伺候你
You know what?
你知道嗎?
Forget about me. Let's give you another turn.
別管我了,我再伺候你一回
-Me,again? -Sure. Why not?
-又是我? -當然,有何不可?
Boy,somebody's gonna get a big fruit basket tomorrow!
明天有人會收到大水果籃!
I gotta tell you,you are nothing like I thought you'd be.
我得告訴你,你不像我想像中的那樣
How do you mean?
什麼意思?
I had you pegged as a guy who's always,"Me,me,me!"
大概是我認為,你是只顧自己享受的人
But you,you're a giver.
但你是個樂於付出的人
You're the most generous man I ever met.
你是我見過最慷慨的人
I mean,you're practically a woman.
你簡直就是個女人
-You're just saying that. -No.
-你剛剛說了那個 -不
A woman!
一個女人
-So? -I missed him.
-所以? -我錯過了
-I'm so sorry. -That's too bad.
-我很抱歉 -這太糟了
Yeah,right.
是的
No,I feel bad for her. I do.
不,我覺得對她不好,我真的這麼認為
I can think of somebody other than myself.
我可以考慮其他人多過考慮我自己
All right,I'm going to bed.
好吧,我要去睡覺了
-Happy birthday. Hang in there. -Thanks.
-生日快樂.保持狀態 -謝謝
Yes!
好啊!
Pizza coupons.
匹薩優惠券
Okay. You guys want help cleaning up this mess?
你們小伙打算幫忙清理這裡嗎?
That'd be great.
不錯
So,Rach,you wanna save this wrapping paper?
瑞秋,這包裝紙要留下來嗎?
Are you gonna go for it with Ross or should I throw it out?
你要為羅斯留下,還是要我丟掉?
I don't know. I don't know.
我不知道,我不知道
Thought about it all the way there...
我左思右想
...and I thought about it all the way back. You know,it's Ross!
我左思右想,你知道的,羅斯
You know what I mean? It's Ross.
你知道什麼我什麼意思?就是羅斯了
-Sure! -Sure.
-當然! -當然
I don't know. This is just my initial gut feeling...
我不知道,這是我內心深處的感受
... but I'm thinking it'd be really great.
我想這樣應該會很不錯
Oh,my God,me too! We'd be like friends-in-law!
天啊,我也是這樣想 這樣我們就成了親戚兼朋友
The best part is you already know all about him.
你知道最棒的是什麼?最棒的就是你已對他瞭如指掌
You start on the 1 5th date.
就好像從第15次約會開始
But it would be like starting on the 1 5th date.
對,但這就像從第15次約會開始
Another good point.
這觀點也不錯
I mean,on the 1 5th date, you're already in a very...
不,在第15次約會時,感情已
... "relationship-y" place. You're committed.
相當深厚,你們已經定下來了
What happens if it doesn't work out?
如果感情破裂該怎麼辦?
-Why isn't it working out? -Sometimes it doesn't.
-為何會感情破裂? -感情是勉強不來的
Is he not cute enough? Does he not make enough money?
你不覺得他帥?他錢賺得不夠多?
-No,I'm just -Maybe there's someone else.
-不,我只是 -或許是另有其人?
-ls there someone else? -No,there is no one else.
-另有其人? -沒有,沒有另有其人
Then why are you dumping my brother?
那麼你為何甩掉我哥?
Hey,big Spender!
大…揮霍者
She's still asleep.
她還在睡覺
-So how'd it go? -You know how you think you're great?
-情況如何? -你有沒有老覺得自己床上功夫不錯?
The fact you'd even ask shows how little you know me.
你會問這種問題,表示你根本不瞭解我
Last night I couldn't do the thing that usually makes me great.
昨晚我不能做讓自己滿足的事
So I had to do all this other stuff.
因此我得搬出全套功夫
And the response I got! Man,oh,man!
結果我得到什麼回應?
It was like a ticker-tape parade!
就像是盛大的遊行
I know. My room's very,very close to the parade route.
我明白,遊行發生時,我的房間就非常接近遊行路線
It was amazing,and not just for her. For me too!
這簡直是太神奇了,而且不只是對她,對我也一樣
It's like,all of a sudden I'm blind...
我就好像突然失明
... but all my other senses are heightened.
但其他的感官卻更加的敏感
It's like I was able to appreciate it...
好像我達到…
...on another level.
…更高的境界
-I didn't know you had another level. -I know. Neither did l!
-我不知道你還有更高的境界. -我懂,我自己也不知道
Is something going on with O.J.?
O.J有活動?
Hey,great skirt. Birthday present?
漂亮的裙子,生日禮物?
-From who? -You.
-誰送的? -你
I exchanged the blouse you got me.
我將你送的襯衫改成的
Well,it's the thought.
真聰明
Doesn't Ross'flight get in in a couple hours? At gate 27B?
羅斯的飛機不是再過幾小時就要抵達?27-b門?
Yeah. Monica,you know,I've been thinking about it.
對,摩尼卡,我一直在想
I've decided this Ross thing is not a good idea.
我雖決定和羅斯在一起,但這樣或許不好
Why?
為什麼?
I feel like I wouldn't just be going out with him.
因為我感覺,我不只是和他出去
I'd be going out with all of you. There'd be pressure
而是和你們大家一起出去,因為壓力…
No pressure,no pressure!
不,沒有壓力.沒有壓力…
Nothing has happened, and you're already so
八字都還沒一撇你就…
I'm not "so." Okay,I was a teensy bit weird at first...
我沒有,開始我也覺得有點奇怪
... but I'll be good. I promise.
但我沒事的,我保證
-Who is it? -It's me,Carl.
-是誰? -是我,卡爾
-Come on up. -Behind my brother's back?
-上來! -背著我哥?
Is the kind of crazy thing you won't be hearing from me.
我就不做出這種瘋狂事
-Seven hundred bucks! -All right,you did it!
-七百塊! -你辦到了!
Do we have any fruit?
我們有水果可吃嗎?
Man,hell of a two weeks.
折騰了兩星期
You know what? I feel I learned something.
我感覺自己學到了一些
You'll stick with this "all for her" thing?
這麼說你將繼續「犧牲小我完成大我」?
What are you,crazy?
你瘋了不成
When a blind man gets his sight back, does he walk around like this?
瞎人重新見光明後會這樣走路嗎?
If I see one more picture of Ed Begley Jr...
我是說如果我再看見艾德貝格拉二世
...in that stupid electric car, I'm gonna shoot myself!
在那電車上,我就舉槍自盡
I'm not against environmental issues,per se...
別誤會我的意思,我個人並不反對環保
...it's just that guy!
只是我討厭那傢伙
I can't believe you'd rather go out with him than me.
我難以相信你跟他約會,而不是跟我
Excuse me,I'm trying to have a date here.
抱歉,我正在約會
Fine. Just stop thinking about me.
行,那就別再想我
Can't do it,can you?
辦不到,對不?
I'm thinking about you. So what?
我想你,那又怎樣?
I don't get it. What do you see in this guy?
我不懂你為何會選上這種人?
Happens to be a very nice guy.
他像是個好男人
I mean,come on,buddy! Get a real car!
老兄,買台真正的車吧
Rachel,come on. Give us a chance.
瑞秋,給我一個機會吧
Ross,it's too hard.
羅斯,太難了
Why,because it'll get weird for everyone else? This is about us.
為什麼?因為大家會感覺不對勁?這是我們兩人的事
I've been in love with you since the ninth grade.
我從九年級開始就愛上你
You're like my best friend. If we broke up,and I lost you
羅斯,你像是我最要好的朋友 我知道如果分手我將失去你
What makes you think that?
不,你為何認為我們會分手?
Have you been involved where you haven't broken up?
曾和你在一起人不是都和你分手了
No.
不
But it only has to happen once.
但這種事只會發生一次
You and I both know we are perfect for each other. Right?
你我都知道我們是天生的一對
So the only question is: Are you attracted to me?
唯一的問題是:你對我有感覺嗎?
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean,I've never looked at you that way before.
我從未以那種方式看你
Well,start looking.
那就開始看吧
-Wow. -Exactly!
-喔. -準確!
And I'm gonna be the guy...
沒錯,我就是那個
...caught behind this hammerhead in traffic!
被困在車陣中的傢伙
Right! You're right.
對…你是對的
You know what?
你知道嗎?
I'm supposed to pick up a friend at the airport.
我本應該去機場接朋友
I am so sorry!
真是抱歉
If you wanna finish your drinks, please do.
如果你想在這兒繼續喝,請便
-I'm sorry,I gotta go. I'm sorry. -But....
-但我得走了,抱歉 -可是
-Where are you going? -To get Ross.
-你要去哪? -去接羅斯
-My God,this is so exciting! -I know.
-天哪,這太令人興奮了! -我知道
If you want the rest of my date, I'm not gonna finish it.
如果你希望和我繼續剩下的約會,我要結束這個
-Rachel,he's not a sandwich. -No,he's a banker with opera tickets.
-瑞秋,他不是三明治. -不,他是一個有劇院的銀行家
Hello!
你好!
-Where you going? -Airport.
-你要去哪? -機場
You can't tell him. There's so much I haven't done.
你不能告訴他,有太多的事情我沒有去做
I haven't watched Baywatch with Yasmine Bleeth!
我還沒有看「海灣女郎」呢!
Chandler,relax. This is a good going to the airport.
錢德,輕鬆點,這是一個好的接機
Oh,well then fly,good woman, fly like the wind.
哦,好吧,飛吧,好女人,像風一樣飛吧
-I'm flying! -Tell him I'm the one who blew it!
-我在飛也! -告訴他是我吹的風!
Yes,another successful case for the love doctor.
好吧,另外一個愛情博士的成功案例
Excuse me! Pardon me. Excuse me. Sorry.
對不起!對不起
Toby,for God's sake, will you let it go?
桃伊,別再胡思亂想了
There's no Rachel!
沒有瑞秋這個人
Hey! I got that.
嘿,我拿到了
-Thanks,sweetie. -No problem.
-謝謝 -不客氣
I can't wait for you to meet my friends.
我迫不及待、想將你介紹給我朋友
You don't think they'll judge me?
你不認為他們會評斷我、取笑我?
-No,they will. I just.... -Can't wait!
-他們會的,我只是… -但我實在是等不及
Come on,they're gonna love you.
他們一定會喜歡你的
-==六人行第一季完==- -=敬請期待第二季=- -bbs.btbbt.com-